[
    {
        "question": "What department handles fake blood?",
        "options": ["SFX", "Hair", "Makeup", "Art"],
        "answer": "Makeup"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What walkie talkie channel is production usually on?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "answer": "1"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Which departments work under the lighting director?",
        "options": ["G&E", "Camera", "Audio", "Art"],
        "answer": "G&E"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What happens when someone not in cast or crew gets on camera?",
        "options": ["An apology", "An insult", "Person signs release", "Production pays them"],
        "answer": "Person signs release"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What word(s) lets the medic know that they are needed but NOT urgently?",
        "options": ["Bloodless", "No ambulance", "Non-emergency", "No biggie"],
        "answer": "Non-emergency"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What color are crew members asked to wear on set?",
        "options": ["Blue", "Gray", "White", "Black"],
        "answer": "Black"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Head of the Electric department?",
        "options": ["Best Boy", "Best Person", "Gaffer", "Key Electrcian"],
        "answer": "Gaffer"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Head of the Grip department?",
        "options": ["Best Boy", "Gaffer", "Key Grip", "Best Boy Grip"],
        "answer": "Key Grip"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Which crew member writes out camera logs?",
        "options": ["Director of Photography", "Camera Operator", "Lighting Director", "Camera Assistant"],
        "answer": "Camera Assistant"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Which member of the audio team usually handles mic'ing up cast?",
        "options": ["Audio Supervisor", "Boom Operator", "Audio Mixer", "A2"],
        "answer": "A2"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Who handles backing up media on set?",
        "options": ["Director of Photography", "Camera Assistant", "Audio Mixer", "Media Manager"],
        "answer": "Media Manager"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What kind of receipt do PAs need for lunch orders?",
        "options": ["Credit Card", "Cash", "Itemized", "None"],
        "answer": "Itemized"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What is the itemized list of equipment required when travelling to foreign countries?",
        "options": ["Quote", "Invoice", "Carnet", "Equipment List"],
        "answer": "Carnet"
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What is the term for clearing out equipment and personnel from a location?",
        "options": ["Exit", "Martini Shot", "Load Out", "Load In"],
        "answer": "Load Out"
    }
]